Jaster Chang

Front-end Developer

Taiwan, Taipei

(+886) 921-240064

⊗

ໍາດ

0

jaster1019@gmail.com /jaster-chang-24250590

ABOUT ME

7 years experience (3 years as front-end, 4 years as full-stack) engineer with extensive experience in development on JavaScript (mostly React), mobile UX optimization, and single page application. Always have willing to learn new things, exploring new technologies.

EXPERTISE

FRONT-END

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript (ES6)

React TypeScript Next.js

CSS Preprocessor (SASS)

Bundling Tool (Webpack)

BACK-END / OTHERS

Node.js LNMP Laravel

Docker Continuous Delivery

Jenkins Github Action

AWS Services

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Engineering

National Cheng Kung University Taiwan, 2006 – 2010

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Engineer

KiWi New Energy | Taiwan | 2021 -

- Developed landing page with Next.js, using Github Action and AWS serverless services to deploy the SPA site
- Build up Continuouse Delivery with Github Action and AWS ECS/ECR to containerize our Back-Office platform

TypeScript React Next.js Chakra UI SASS

Framer-Motion (Animation) Webpack Docker

AWS (ECS, Lamda) Continuous Delivery (Github Action)

Front-end Engineer

Genesis Gaming | Taiwan | 2018 - 2020

- @ Gained active users by 20% by implementing 20 event SPA.
- Participated in Scrum teams across Taipei, Vegas, and Vancouver, implementing widgets used in HTML5 games.
- Optimized performance by taking mobile-first design, using React Hook to reduce rerendering, configuring Webpack to do lazy-loading and chunk JS files.
- Refined continuous delivery flow with Docker and Jenkins.

 React
 Preact
 Redux
 SASS
 XState (State Management)

 React-Spring (Animation)
 Webpack
 Docker
 Jenkins

Full-stack Engineer

UrAD | Taiwan | 2015 - 2017

- Developed a management system for work assignment and finance report generation, decreasing redundant costs on digital advertising.
- Bring in Scrum and Kanban to improve teamwork.

Vue Webpack LNMP Laravel

Full-stack Engineer

HWTrek | Taiwan | 2014 - 2015

Jr. Full-stack Engineer

iwant | Taiwan | 2012 - 2013